MS

Mackenzie Smith

Professional Summary

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

Work History

Rolling Plains Construction - Estimating Intern Apache Junction, AZ 07/2018 - Current

- Analyzed project drawings to prepare estimates for fireproofing work
- Searched through job documents to find new projects to bid on
- Digitized architectural and structural drawings
- Updated and recorded financial and project reports

OneStop Nutrition - Sales Associate Phoenix, United States 06/2017 - 07/2018

- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales
- Retained product, service, and company policy to serve each customers specific goals

InnerVision Yoga - Receptionist Phoenix, NY 05/2017 - 07/2018

- Greeted incoming visitors and customers professionally and provided friendly, knowledgeable assistance
- Answered telephone calls to field inquiries from clients, vendors and various other callers seeking information
- Kept reception area clean and neat to give visitors positive first impression

Mackenzie3030@yahoo.com (602) 505-5229 Phoenix, AZ 85013

Skills

- HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- Photoshop
- Communication
- Time Management
- Positive Attitude
- Critical Thinking
- Judgement and Decision Making

Education

12/2019

Arizona State University

Tempe, AZ

Bachelor of Integrative Science And

Arts: Interdisciplinary Studies

- Focus Areas of Business and Media Analysis
- Graduated with 3.4 GPA
- Recipient of New American University Scholar - Provost's Award Scholarship

Hobbies

Passionate about self growth - physical and mental. I enjoy being able to push myself past my own limitations, and be in control of my own results.

The physical aspect is a huge part of my life. I love daily gym sessions, yoga, and hiking with my dogs.